Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Domestic Advertisements, part 1, 1875-2001 and undated, bulk 1920s-1990s RL.00687
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Main Files Series, 1875-2001 and undated
  - Eli Lilly, 1968-1993
    - 1968-1969, 1971, 1974-1975, 1977-1983, 1988-1993 (Box EL1)
  - Employees Insurance of Wausau, 1953-1971
    - 1953-1965 (Box EI1)
    - 1966-1971 (Box EI2)
  - First National City Bank, 1958-1971
    - 1958, 1966-1971 (Box FN1)
  - Ford Dealer Association, 1944-1997
    For related materials see the J. Walter Thompson Co. Detroit Office, Detroit Office Records; Ford Dealer Association Records; Ford Collateral Literature.
    - 1944, 1946-1947 (Box FD1)
    - 1947-1948 (Box FD2)
    - 1949 (Box FD3-FD4)
    - 1950 (Box FD5)
    - 1950-1952 (Box FD6)
    - 1953-1956 (Box FD7)
    - 1957-1959 (Box FD8)
    - 1960-1962 (Box FD9)
    - 1962 (Box FD10)
    - 1962-1963 (Box FD11)
    - 1963 (Box FD12)
    - 1964 (Box FD13-FD14)
    - 1965 (Box FD15-FD16)
    - 1965-1966 (Box FD17)
    - 1966 (Box FD18-FD19)
    - 1966-1967 (Box FD20)
    - 1967 (Box FD21-FD23)
    - 1967-1968 (Box FD24)
    - 1968 (Box FD25-FD26)
    - 1969 (Box FD27-FD29)
    - 1970 (Box FD30-FD32)
    - 1971 (Box FD33-FD35)
    - 1972 (Box FD36-FD38)
    - 1973 (Box FD39-FD40)
    - 1974 (Box FD41)
    - 1975-1977 (Box FD42)
    - 1978 (Box FD43)
    - 1979-1981 (Box FD44)
    - 1982-1989 (Box FD45)
    - 1990-1997 (Box FD46)
    - 1962-1996 and undated, oversize additions, 8 folders (Box FD47)
      Part of accession 04-0010.
  - Ford Dealer's Advertising Fund, 1973-1984
    - 1973 (Box FA1)
    - 1974-1975 (Box FA2)
    - 1976-1984 (Box FA3)
  - Ford Motor Co., 1931-1998
    Key campaigns include There's a Ford in Your Future (1945-1948), the Peanuts campaign (1960-1962) and the launch of the Mustang (1964). In addition to print advertisements showing the introduction of new models, photostats of outdoor billboards in the 1940s and early 1950s are included. Truck and dealer advertising can also be found throughout the years.
    Additional information and documentation for the Ford account may be found in other collections including: JWT Co. Newsletters, Winfield Taylor Papers, Norman Strouse Papers (a small collection), Legal and Financial Documents, and Writings and Speeches. The Ford Collateral Literature files include showroom brochures, and diverse sales materials in many formats
    Folders marked cars do not include any model that has its own folder for a particular year. Cars include station wagons and minivans. Aerostar is a minivan after 1986.
    Folders marked trucks include all truck sizes unless there is a folder specifically for medium/heavy duty trucks, in which case the trucks folder would contain light trucks (Ranger, F series, etc. pickups). Bronco is classified as both a truck (1966-1989) and an SUV (1990-).
    Vans includes RVs, conversion and 15 passenger vans, but not minivans.
    Throughout this list, General folders refers to car advertising for Ford cars in general or more than one model in a given ad.
    [See also Oversize Boxes OV5-OV16; Oversize Folders 17-19.]
    - 1944
      - General (Box FM1)
      - General (Anglo-Jewish publications) (Box FM1)
      - Dealer (including parts) (Box FM1)
      - Johansson Divison (gage blocks) (Box FM1)
      - Radio programs ( Presented by Mr. and Mrs. Henry Ford) (Box FM1)
    - 1944-1945 Lincoln and Mercury (Box FM1)
    - 1945
      - General (Box FM1)
    - 1946
      - General (Box FM1)
      - Insertion schedules (Box FM1)
      - Publication: The ABC of Ford Truck Selling (Box FM1)
      - Publications--Comics (Box FM2)
    - 1947
      - General, 2 folders (Box FM2)
      - Comics (Box FM2)
      - Radio shows (Fred Allen) (Box FM2)
    - 1947 Insertion schedules (no advertisements), 3 folders (Box FM3)
    - 1947-1950 (From Norman Strouse scrapbook)
      - 1947 (Box FM4)
        - Automotive News series (Box FM4)
      - 1949
        - Automotive News series (Box FM4)
        - Collier's bleed Adaptations (Box FM4)
        - Comics (Box FM4)
        - Harper's Bazaar (Box FM4)
        - Magazine advertisements
          - Black-and-white (Box FM4)
          - Color (Box FM4)
          - Women's (Box FM4)
        - Outdoor (Box FM4)
        - Science publications (Box FM4)
      - 1950
        - Collier's bleed adaptations (Box FM4)
        - Comics (Box FM4)
        - Magazine advertisements
          - Black-and-white (Box FM4)
          - Color (Box FM4)
          - Women's (Box FM4)
    - 1948
      - Comics (Box FM5)
      - General and insertion schedules (Box FM5)
      - Industrial and marine engine sales (Box FM5)
      - Outdoor (Box FM5)
      - Parts (Box FM5)
      - Products made in England (Anglia, Prefect, etc.) (Box FM5)
    - 1949
      - Advertisements
        - General (Box FM6)
        - Comics (Box FM6)
        - Comics--Photostats (Box FM6)
        - Contests (Box FM6)
        - Drafts (Box FM6)
        - Outdoor (Box FM6)
        - Parts (Box FM7)
        - Products made in England (Box FM7)
        - Television programs (Box FM7)
        - Tractors, buses, taxis, engines (Box FM7)
        - Trucks, including dealers, 2 folders (Box FM7)
      - Insertion schedules (Box FM8)
        - Magazines and comics (Box FM8)
        - Newspapers
          - New York (Box FM8)
          - Pittsburgh (Box FM8)
          - Washington and Somerville (Box FM8)
    - 1950
      - General, 3 folders (Box FM9)
      - Comics (Box FM9)
      - Country Squire, Crestliner (Box FM9)
      - English-built models (Box FM9)
    - 1950
      - Insertion schedules (Box FM10)
      - Outdoor (Box FM10)
      - Parts (Box FM10)
      - Taxi, school bus (Box FM10)
      - Television (Box FM10)
      - Trucks (Box FM10)
    - 1951
      - General, 2 folders (Box FM11)
      - Comics (Box FM11)
      - Industrial Arts Awards (Box FM11)
      - Insertion schedules (Box FM12)
      - Parts (Box FM12)
      - Trucks (Box FM12)
      - Victoria (Box FM12)
    - 1952
      - Buses and taxis (Box FM13)
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM13)
        - English-built models (Box FM13)
        - Ranch Wagon, Sunliner (Box FM13)
        - Victoria (Box FM13)
      - Comics (Box FM13)
      - Industrial (Box FM13)
      - Industrial Arts Awards (Box FM13)
      - Outdoor, 2 folders (Box FM13)
      - Parts (Box FM14)
      - Television and radio (Box FM14)
      - Tractors (Box FM14)
      - Trucks, 2 folders (Box FM14)
    - 1953
      - General (Box FM15)
      - Bus and taxi (Box FM15)
      - Comics (Box FM15)
      - English-built models (Box FM15)
      - Ford Theatre (Box FM15)
      - Industrial (Box FM15)
      - Outdoor (Box FM15)
      - Parts (Box FM15)
      - Poster Annual (Box FM16)
      - Tractor (Box FM16)
      - Trucks (Box FM16)
    - 1953-1954, General (Box FM16)
    - 1954
      - Cars
        - General, 2 folders (Box FM16)
        - English-built models (Box FM17)
        - Ranch Wagon and Skyliner (Box FM17)
        - Thunderbird (Box FM17)
      - Comics (Box FM17)
      - Industrial (Box FM17)
      - Outdoor (Box FM17)
      - Parts (Box FM17)
      - Television and radio (Box FM17)
      - Tractor, bus (Box FM17)
      - Trucks (Box FM17)
    - 1955
      - Action Reports (trucks and tractors) (Box FM17)
      - English-built models (Box FM17)
    - 1955-1957 Ford-produced television programs, 6 folders (Box FM18)
    - 1956
      - Cars (Box FM19)
        - General, 2 folders (Box FM19)
        - English-built models (Box FM19)
        - Station wagons (Box FM19)
        - Thunderbird (Box FM19)
      - Comics (Box FM19)
      - Industrial Arts Awards (Box FM19)
      - Outdoor (Box FM20)
      - Parts (Box FM20)
      - Recruitment (Box FM20)
      - Trucks (Box FM20)
    - 1957
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM20)
        - English-built models (Box FM20)
        - Sunliner, Skyliner, station wagons (Box FM20)
      - Comics, 2 folders (Box FM20)
      - Outdoor (Box FM20)
      - Parts (Box FM20)
      - Trucks (Box FM20)
    - 1958
      - Cars (Box FM21)
        - General (including Edsel, Lincoln, Mercury) (Box FM21)
        - English-built models (Box FM21)
        - Skyliner, Sunliner, station wagons (Box FM21)
        - Taunus 17M (Germany) (Box FM21)
        - Thunderbird, 2 folders (Box FM21)
      - Comics (Box FM21)
      - Dealers (Box FM21)
      - Insertion schedules (Box FM21)
      - Television (Box FM21)
      - Trucks, 2 folders (Box FM21)
    - 1959
      - Cars (Box FM22)
        - General (Box FM22)
        - English-built models (Box FM22)
        - Fairlane, Galaxie (Box FM22)
        - Taunus 17M (Germany) (Box FM22)
        - Thunderbird (Box FM22)
      - Outdoor (Box FM22)
      - Overseas (military/diplomatic) (Box FM22)
      - Parts (Box FM22)
      - Tractors (Box FM22)
      - Trucks, 3 folders (Box FM22)
    - 1960
      - American Legion Junior Baseball progam (Box FM23)
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM23)
        - English-built models (Box FM23)
        - Falcon (Box FM23)
        - Falcon-- Peanuts advertisements (Box FM23)
        - Galaxie, Starliner (Box FM23)
        - Taunus 17M (Germany) (Box FM23)
        - Taxis, police cars (Box FM23)
        - Thunderbird (Box FM23)
      - Industrial Arts Awards (Box FM24)
      - Outdoor (Box FM24)
      - Parts (Box FM24)
      - Trucks
        - General (Box FM24)
        - Farm use (Box FM24)
    - 1961
      - Cars (Box FM25)
        - Falcon (Box FM25)
        - Thunderbird (Box FM25)
      - Trucks
        - Magazine (Box FM25)
        - Newspaper (Box FM25)
    - 1961-1962
      - Advertisements in foreign languages (Box FM25)
    - 1962
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM25)
        - Fairlane (Box FM25)
        - Falcon (Box FM25)
        - Galaxie (Box FM25)
        - Mercury, Comet (Box FM25)
      - FALS (Ford Authorized Leasing System) (Box FM25)
      - Industrial engines (Box FM25)
      - Parts (Box FM25)
      - Tractors (Box FM25)
      - Trucks, 4 folders (Box FM26)
    - 1963
      - Advertisements in foreign languages (Box FM27)
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM27)
        - Fairlane (Box FM27)
        - Falcon (Box FM27)
        - Galaxie (Box FM27)
        - Taunus (Germany), Cortina (England) (Box FM27)
        - Taxis, police cars (Box FM27)
        - Thunderbird (Box FM27)
      - FALS (Box FM27)
      - Industrial motors (Box FM28)
      - Parts (Box FM28)
      - Report to Ford Dealers (including television program advertisements) (Box FM28)
      - Trucks, 3 folders (Box FM28)
    - 1963-1964, Fordson tractors (Box FM28)
    - 1964
      - Advertisements in foreign languages (Box FM29)
      - Cars
        - General, 2 folders (Box FM29)
        - Comet (Box FM29)
        - Consul, Corsair (England) (Box FM29)
        - Fairlane (Box FM29)
        - Falcon (Box FM29)
        - Mercury (Box FM29)
        - Mustang, 2 folders (Box FM30)
        - Taxis (Box FM30)
        - Thunderbird (Box FM30)
      - FALS (Box FM30)
      - Industrial engines (Box FM30)
      - Parts (Box FM30)
      - Trucks, 2 folders (Box FM30)
    - 1965
      - Advertisements in foreign languages (Box FM31)
      - Cars
        - General, 2 folders (Box FM31)
        - Comet (Box FM31)
        - Cortina, Corsair, Taunus (European models) (Box FM32)
        - Fairlane (Box FM32)
        - Falcon (Box FM32)
        - Galaxie (Box FM32)
        - Mustang (Box FM32)
        - Police, taxi (Box FM32)
        - Thunderbird (Box FM32)
      - FALS (Box FM32)
      - Industrial engines (Box FM32)
      - Parts (Box FM33)
      - Trucks, 3 folders (Box FM33)
    - 1966 (Box FM34)
      - Advertisements in foreign languages (Box FM34)
      - Cars
        - General (including international and military sales), 3 folders (Box FM34)
        - Corsair, Taurus, Zephyr, Zodiac (Box FM34)
        - Fairlane (Box FM34)
        - Falcon (Box FM34)
        - Galaxie (Box FM34)
        - Mustang (Box FM34)
        - Police, taxi (Box FM34)
        - Thunderbird (Box FM34)
      - Industrial engine (Box FM34)
      - Parts (Box FM34)
      - Rent-a-Car (Box FM34)
      - Trucks, 3 folders (Box FM35)
    - 1967 (Box FM36)
      - Cars
        - General, 2 folders (Box FM36)
        - Cougar, Corsair, Cortina, Taunus (Box FM36)
        - Fairlane (Box FM36)
        - Mustang (Box FM36)
        - Thunderbird (Box FM36)
      - Comics (Box FM36)
      - FALS (Box FM36)
      - Industrial engines (Box FM36)
      - Trucks, 2 folders (Box FM36)
    - 1967-1968
      - Advertisements in foreign languages (Box FM36)
      - Television series (Box FM36)
    - 1968
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM36)
        - Cortina, 20M, 17M, Escort, Cougar (Box FM36)
        - Maverick (Box FM36)
        - Mustang (Box FM36)
        - Thunderbird (Box FM36)
        - Torino (Box FM36)
      - FALS (Box FM36)
      - Trucks, 2 folders (Box FM37)
    - 1968-1969
      - Police (Box FM37)
    - 1969
      - Advertisements in foreign languages (Box FM37)
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM37)
        - Cobra (Box FM37)
        - Cortina (Box FM37)
        - LTD (Box FM37)
        - Maverick (Box FM37)
        - Mustang (Box FM37)
        - Thunderbird (Box FM37)
        - Torino (Box FM37)
        - Wagons (Box FM37)
      - FALS (Box FM38)
      - Punt, Pass and Kick (Box FM38)
      - Trucks, 2 folders (Box FM38)
      - Vans (Box FM38)
    - 1969-1970, More Than a Second Car program (Box FM38)
    - 1970
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM38)
        - Maverick (Box FM38)
        - Mustang (Box FM38)
        - Thunderbird (Box FM38)
        - Torino, Cobra, Ford Performance Digest (Box FM38)
      - Detroit Symphony (Box FM39)
      - Foreign language (Box FM39)
      - Military, diplomatic (Box FM39)
      - Rent-a-Car (Box FM39)
      - Television series (Box FM39)
      - Trucks
        - General (Box FM39)
        - Bronco, Ranchero (Box FM39)
        - Heavy duty (Box FM39)
      - Vans (Box FM39)
    - 1971
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM39)
        - Maverick (Box FM39)
        - Mustang (Box FM39)
        - Pinto (Box FM39)
        - Thunderbird (Box FM39)
        - Torino (Box FM39)
      - Television, Punt, Pass and Kick program (Box FM39)
      - Trucks
        - General (Box FM39)
        - American Trucking Association (ATA) (Box FM39)
        - Bronco (Box FM39)
        - Heavy duty (Box FM39)
      - Vans (Box FM39)
    - 1972 (Box FM40)
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM40)
        - Galaxie LTD (Box FM40)
        - Maverick, Thunderbird (Box FM40)
        - Pinto (Box FM40)
        - Torino (Box FM40)
      - Diplomatic, military, rentals, television (Box FM40)
      - Trucks
        - General (Box FM40)
        - Heavy duty (Box FM40)
        - Ranchero, Bronco (Box FM40)
      - Vans (Box FM40)
    - 1972-1973
      - General (Box FM40)
      - Television (Bob Hope) (Box FM40)
    - 1973
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM40)
        - Thunderbird, Torino (Box FM40)
      - Trucks
        - General (Box FM40)
        - American Trucking Association (ATA) (Box FM40)
        - Bronco (Box FM40)
        - Heavy duty (Box FM40)
        - Ranchero (Box FM40)
      - Vans (Box FM40)
    - 1974 (Box FM41)
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM41)
        - Torino, LTD (Box FM41)
      - Diplomatic, military (Box FM41)
      - Television (Box FM41)
      - Trucks
        - General (including American Trucking Association) (Box FM41)
        - Bronco, Ranchero (Box FM41)
        - Heavy duty (Box FM41)
      - Vans (Box FM41)
    - 1975
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM41)
        - Granada (Box FM41)
        - Thunderbird (Box FM41)
      - Trucks
        - General (Box FM41)
        - Heavy duty (Box FM41)
      - Vans (Box FM41)
      - World International Tennis Classic (Box FM41)
    - 1975
      - Trucks (Box FM41)
    - 1976 (Box FM42)
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM42)
        - Mustang, Maverick (Box FM42)
        - Pinto (Box FM42)
        - Thunderbird, Granada (Box FM42)
        - Torino, LTD (Box FM42)
      - Trucks
        - General (Box FM42)
        - Courier (Box FM42)
        - Heavy duty (Box FM42)
      - Vans (Box FM42)
      - World International Tennis Classic (Box FM42)
    - 1977
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM42)
        - LTD, Granada (Box FM42)
        - Mustang, Thunderbird (Box FM42)
        - Pinto (Box FM42)
      - Diplomatic, military (Box FM42)
      - Trucks
        - General (Box FM42)
        - Bronco, Courier, Ranchero (Box FM42)
        - Heavy duty (Box FM42)
      - Vans (Box FM42)
      - World International Tennis Classic (Box FM42)
    - 1978 (Box FM43)
      - Cars
        - General (including Fiesta) (Box FM43)
        - Fairmont (Box FM43)
        - Granada, LTD (Box FM43)
        - Mustang, Thunderbird, Pinto (Box FM43)
      - Diplomatic, military, police, World International Tennis Classic (Box FM43)
      - Foreign language advertisements (Box FM43)
      - Trucks
        - General (Box FM43)
        - Bronco, Courier, Ranchero (Box FM43)
        - Heavy duty (Box FM43)
      - Vans (Box FM43)
    - 1979
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM43)
        - Fairmont (Box FM43)
        - Mustang, Thunderbird (Box FM43)
        - Pinto (Box FM43)
      - Military, diplomatic (Box FM43)
      - Trucks
        - General (Box FM43)
        - Bronco, Courier, Ranchero (Box FM43)
        - Medium and heavy duty (including foreign language advertisements) (Box FM43)
      - Vans (Box FM43)
    - 1980 (Box FM44)
      These 1980 folders may include advertisements for 1980 models which were actually produced in 1979.
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM44)
        - Mustang, Thunderbird (Box FM44)
      - Corporate (Box FM44)
      - Posters (Box FM44)
      - Trucks
        - General (Box FM44)
        - Medium and heavy duty (Box FM44)
      - Vans (Box FM44)
    - 1981
      - Cars (Box FM44)
      - Trucks (Box FM44)
      - Vans (Box FM44)
    - 1981-1982
      - Corporate, FALS (Box FM44)
    - 1982 (Box FM45)
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM45)
        - Mustang (Box FM45)
      - Trucks
        - Light (Box FM45)
        - Medium and heavy duty (Box FM45)
      - Vans (Box FM45)
    - 1983
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM45)
        - Mustang, Thunderbird (Box FM45)
      - Corporate and FALS, Rental Sweepstakes (Box FM45)
      - Trucks, Vans (Box FM45)
    - 1984 (Box FM46)
      - Cars
        - Escort (Box FM46)
        - LTD (Box FM46)
        - Mustang (Box FM46)
        - Tempo (Box FM46)
        - Thunderbird (Box FM46)
      - Performance and racing (Box FM46)
      - Trucks (Box FM46)
      - Vans, station wagons (Box FM46)
    - 1985
      - Cars (Box FM46)
      - Performance, racing (Box FM46)
      - Trucks (Box FM46)
    - 1985-1986
      - Corporate (Box FM46)
    - 1986
      - Cars (Box FM46)
      - Fleet, direct marketing (Box FM46)
      - Performance and racing (Box FM46)
      - Trucks (Box FM46)
    - 1987 (Box FM47)
      - Cars (Box FM47)
      - Corporate, racing, fleet, FALS (Box FM47)
      - Trucks
        - Light (Box FM47)
        - Medium and heavy duty (Box FM47)
      - Vans, minivans (Box FM47)
    - 1988
      - Cars (Box FM47)
      - Performance, racing, military, FALS (Box FM47)
      - Trucks, vans (Box FM47)
    - 1989
      - Cars
        - General (Box FM47)
        - Taurus (Box FM47)
      - Performance, racing (Box FM47)
      - Trucks and vans
        - Light (Box FM47)
        - Medium and heavy duty (Box FM47)
    - 1990
      - Cars, SUVs (Box FM47)
      - Corporate (Box FM47)
      - Industrial (Box FM47)
      - Trucks, mobile homes, minivans (Box FM47)
    - 1991 (Box FM48)
      - Cars (Box FM48)
      - Corporate (Box FM48)
      - Industrial (Box FM48)
      - Trucks, RVs, SUVs, minivans (Box FM48)
    - 1992
      - Cars (Box FM48)
      - Corporate, racing (Box FM48)
      - SUVs, minivans (Box FM48)
      - Trucks, vans (Box FM48)
    - 1993
      - Cars (Box FM48)
      - Corporate, racing (Box FM48)
      - RVs (Box FM48)
      - Trucks (Box FM48)
    - 1993-1994
      - Industrial (Box FM48)
    - 1994
      - Cars, SUVs (Box FM48)
      - Corporate (Box FM48)
      - Mustang (Box FM48)
      - Trucks (Box FM48)
    - 1994-1995 (Box FM49)
      - Corporate (Box FM49)
    - 1995
      - Cars, minivans (Box FM49)
      - Industrial (Box FM49)
      - SUVs (Box FM49)
      - Trucks (Box FM49)
    - 1996
      - Cars, minivans (Box FM49)
      - Corporate (Box FM49)
      - Industrial (Box FM49)
      - SUVs (Box FM49)
      - Trucks (Box FM49)
    - 1997
      - Cars (Box FM49)
      - Corporate (Box FM49)
      - Industrial (Box FM49)
      - SUVs, trucks (Box FM49)
    - 1998
      - Cars (Box FM49)
      - Corporate (Box FM49)
      - SUVs (Box FM49)
    - Ford Motor Co. Addition 2004-0010 (Box FM50)
      - 1945-1969
        - 1945-1948, General (Box FM50)
        - 1950-1959, General (Box FM50)
        - 1961-1963, Galaxie (Box FM50)
        - 1961-1967, Falcon (Box FM50)
        - 1962, Fordson tractor (Box FM50)
        - 1962-1968, General (Box FM50)
        - 1964-1967
          - Galaxie (Box FM50)
          - Mustang (Box FM50)
        - 1964-1969, Thunderbird (Box FM50)
        - 1965-1967, Pickup truck (Box FM50)
        - 1967-1968, Torino (Box FM50)
        - 1968, Cobra (Box FM50)
        - 1968-1969
          - LTD (Box FM50)
          - Mustang (Box FM50)
          - XL (Box FM50)
        - 1969, Maverick (Box FM50)
        - 1960s, Fairlane (Box FM50)
      - 1970-1987 (Box FM51)
        - 1970, 1977, 1979, General (Box FM51)
        - 1971, 1978, 1979, Mustang (Box FM51)
        - 1972, 1974, 1978 and undated, Pinto (Box FM51)
        - 1975-1979, Granada (Box FM51)
        - 1977-1978, Futura (Box FM51)
        - 1978 and undated, Fiesta (Box FM51)
        - ca. 1970s
          - Cars: LTD, Maverick, Thunderbird, Torino (Box FM51)
          - Heavy duty trucks (Box FM51)
          - Trucks: Bronco, Courier, pickup, Ranchero, vans (Box FM51)
        - 1980-1983, Mustang (Box FM51)
        - 1980-1982, 1984, Aerostar, Ranger, truck, van (Box FM51)
        - 1980-1984, Escort, Granada, Tempo (Box FM51)
        - 1980-1985, Thunderbird (Box FM51)
        - 1981-1983, EXP, Fiesta (Box FM51)
        - 1981-1984
          - Crown Victoria, LTD (Box FM51)
          - General (Box FM51)
        - 1982-1984, Bronco (Box FM51)
        - 1984-1985, Mustang (Box FM51)
        - 1986-1987
          - Corporate and general (Box FM51)
          - Escort, EXP (Box FM51)
          - Mustang (Box FM51)
          - Taurus (Box FM51)
          - Thunderbird (Box FM51)
          - Trucks: Bronco, F-Series, Ranger (Box FM51)
        - 1987
          - Aerostar, commercial trucks (Box FM51)
          - Festiva (Box FM51)
          - Tempo (Box FM51)
      - 1988-1991 (Box FM52)
        - 1988-1989
          - Bronco (Box FM52)
          - Commercial trucks (Box FM52)
          - F-Series truck, Ranger, Aerostar (Box FM52)
          - Mustang, Thunderbird (Box FM52)
          - Probe (Box FM52)
          - Taurus, Tempo (Box FM52)
        - 1989, Escort (Box FM52)
        - 1990
          - General (Box FM52)
          - Thunderbird (Box FM52)
        - 1990-1991
          - Aerostar, commercial trucks (Box FM52)
          - Escort, Probe (Box FM52)
          - Explorer (Box FM52)
          - F-Series truck (Box FM52)
          - General (Box FM52)
          - Mustang (Box FM52)
          - Ranger (Box FM52)
          - Taurus (Box FM52)
        - 1991
          - Crown Victoria, Escort (Box FM52)
          - Econoline van, Club Wagon (Box FM52)
      - 1992-1993 (Box FM53)
        - 1992
          - Commercial trucks (Box FM53)
          - Corporate, general, racing (Box FM53)
          - Crown Victoria, Taurus (Box FM53)
          - Escort, Mustang (Box FM53)